craftcoffee.com 2013-10-22

# Privacy: Coffee Subscription, Delivered Monthly | Craft Coffee

We take your privacy seriously at Craft Coffee. We will never send you spam, or sell your information to marketers. For the full legalese, see below.

This privacy policy covers the use of the web site located at [http://www.craftcoffee.com](http://www.craftcoffee.com/) and the services provided by Caffeinated Labs, LLC ("Craft Coffee"), including how Craft Coffee treats personal information that Craft Coffee collects and receives. Pursuant to Craft Coffee's Terms of Use, you must be 18 years and older to use this site or have permission from a legal guardian. Therefore, this policy makes no provision for individuals under 18 years old. This policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that Craft Coffee does not own or control, or individuals that Craft Coffee does not employ or manage. 

This policy is effective on October 28, 2010.

## Information Collection and How it is Used

General Information: 
  * Craft Coffee will not sell or disclose your name or email address to third parties without your explicit consent, except as specified in this privacy policy.
  * Craft Coffee collects personal information when you register to use Craft Coffee services or to post content on Craft Coffee. At registration you are asked for your email address and certain other optional information.
  * If you would like to obtain a Seller account, Craft Coffee will ask for your business address, phone number, payment information and other related information.
  * Craft Coffee automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, cookies, and the pages you request.
  * Craft Coffee uses information for the following general purposes: products and services provisioning, billing, identification and authentication, services improvement, contact, research, and anonymous reporting. IP addresses are automatically reported by your browser each time you view a web page. Your IP address is stored in Craft Coffee's user registration databases when you register with Craft Coffee. IP addresses may be used for various research purposes, and/or delivering unique functionality on the Craft Coffee Site.

## Service Announcements

Craft Coffee will send you a welcome email when you sign up for Craft Coffee's services.

Craft Coffee will send you service announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so.

You may not opt-out of service-related communications, which are not promotional in nature. If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option to deactivate your account by emailing help@craftcoffee.com from the email address you signed up with.

## Administrative Messages

Craft Coffee may periodically email you with administrative messages. Craft Coffee will not sell or rent your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without your explicit consent. Your information may be combined with information Craft Coffee collects from other companies and used to improve and personalize services, content and advertising. If you don't wish to receive administrative messages or participate in these programs, simply opt-out by emailing help@craftcoffee.com.

## Choice/Opt-out

If you no longer wish to receive administrative messages, you may opt-out by emailing help@craftcoffee.com. Please note that if you do not wish to receive administrative messages from us, those notices will still govern your use of the Craft Coffee website and service, and you are responsible for reviewing such notices for changes.

## Newsletter Emails

Craft Coffee offers subscriptions to Craft Coffee email newsletters. To opt-in, Craft Coffee will ask for your email address and the newsletter(s) you wish to receive. This email address will be used for only this feature. You may change your subscription or unsubscribe at any time by following the instructions contained in the email.

## Cookies

A cookie is a small data file, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier, that is sent to your browser from a web site's computers and stored on your computer's hard drive. You can configure your browser to accept all cookies, reject all cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set. If you reject all cookies, you may not be able to take full advantage of the Craft Coffee service. Craft Coffee uses its own cookies for a number of purposes, including to: Access your information when you "sign in"; keep track of preferences you specify while you are using Craft Coffee's services; display local product offerings; estimate and report Craft Coffee's total audience size and traffic; and conduct research to improve Craft Coffee's content and services. Craft Coffee cookies do not collect personal information, and Craft Coffee does not combine information collected through cookies with other personal information to tell us who you are or what your username or email address is.

## Information Sharing and Disclosure

Craft Coffee may be required to disclose personally identifiable information under special circumstances, such as to comply with subpoenas or when your actions violate the Craft Coffee Terms of Use. Craft Coffee may disclose personally identifiable information to parties in compliance with Craft Coffee's Copyright and Intellectual Property Policy, as Craft Coffee in Craft Coffee's sole discretion believes necessary or appropriate in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringement, piracy, or other unlawful activity. In such events, Craft Coffee may disclose name, street address, city, state, zip code, country, phone number, email address and company name. Craft Coffee may share aggregated demographic information with business partners.

Craft Coffee is affiliated with a variety of businesses and works closely with them. These businesses may operate stores on the Craft Coffee website or sell items to you from the Craft Coffee website. Craft Coffee may also provide services or sell products jointly with affiliated businesses. Due to the nature of Craft Coffee's business model, when an affiliated business is associated with your transaction, you will share customer information that is related to such transaction with that affiliated business.

Craft Coffee employs other companies and people to perform tasks on our behalf and needs to share your information with them to provide products and services to you. Examples could include but are not limited to fulfilling orders, handling billing disputes, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance and providing customer service.

Craft Coffee will not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with nonaffiliated parties except as specified in this Privacy Policy to provide products or services you have requested or when Craft Coffee has your permission. It may be necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Craft Coffee's Terms of Use, as specified in this Privacy Policy or as otherwise required by law. In some cases, Craft Coffee may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, customer information is typically one of the business assets that is transferred. Craft Coffee will transfer information about you if Craft Coffee is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, Craft Coffee will notify you by email or by putting a prominent notice on the Craft Coffee web site before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

As part of the buying and selling process, you may obtain another Craft Coffee user's email address, shipping address and/or other information. Pursuant to Craft Coffee's Terms of Use, you have a limited license to use this information. This information should be used for only Craft Coffee-related communications or for Craft Coffee-facilitated transactions. Craft Coffee has not granted you a license to use the information for unsolicited commercial messages. Without limiting the foregoing, without express consent from the user, you are not licensed to add any Craft Coffee user to your email or physical mail list.

## Third Parties

Except as otherwise expressly included in this Privacy Policy, this document addresses only the use and disclosure of information Craft Coffee collects from you. If you disclose your information to others, whether they are buyers or sellers on Craft Coffee or throughout the internet, different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of the information you disclose to them. Craft Coffee does not control the privacy policies of third parties, and you are subject to the privacy policies of those third parties where applicable. Craft Coffee is not responsible for the privacy or security practices of other websites on the Internet, even those linked to or from the Craft Coffee site. Craft Coffee encourages you to ask questions before you disclose your personal information to others.

## Editing and Deleting Account Information

You can change your Craft Coffee Account Information at any time. Craft Coffee may send you certain communications relating to the Craft Coffee service, such as service announcements and administrative messages that are considered part of your Craft Coffee account. You can delete your Craft Coffee account by emailing help@craftcoffee.com. Please note that your identification, billing and contact information may remain in Craft Coffee's records for some period.

Craft Coffee limits access to personal information about you to employees who Craft Coffee believes reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs. Your Craft Coffee Account Information is password-protected.

If your personally identifiable information changes you may correct or update it by making the change on your Craft Coffee account page. You may delete or deactivate your account by emailing Customer Support at help@craftcoffee.com. Craft Coffee will respond to your request within 10-20 business days.

## Security

The security of your personal information is important to us. Your Craft Coffee account information is protected by a password for your privacy and security. You need to work to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer by signing off once you have finished using a shared computer. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number) for registration Craft Coffee encrypts that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). Craft Coffee follows generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once Craft Coffee receives it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while Craft Coffee strives to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, Craft Coffee cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on Craft Coffee's Web site, you can email Craft Coffee at help@craftcoffee.com.

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

If this privacy policy is changed, Craft Coffee will post changes so that you are aware of those changes. Craft Coffee reserves the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If Craft Coffee makes material changes to this policy you will be notified here, by email, or other places Craft Coffee deems appropriate.

## Questions

If you have questions or suggestions you can contact Craft Coffee via our contact form or by postal mail to Caffeinated Labs, LLC, Attn: Customer Support; 57 S 4th St, New York, New York 11249. You can also reach us at 877-497-2278.
